downloadroute.com 2011-05-28

# Privacy Statement - Download Route

**Privacy Statement**  
DownloadRoute.com is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the DownloadRoute.com Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the DownloadRoute.com website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

During the administration process of the website, Download Route needs to take over some personal information, in order to personalize the website usage and make it easier for each one of the users. Also, collecting information (such as name, e-mail etc) is useful for DownloadRoute.com in order to adapt our ads to your preferences. DownloadRoute.com respects and grants confidentiality for personal data collected over from its users at several different points on the website. We are the sole owners of the information gathered within the Download Route.com website. We shall not sell or rent this information to others in any way. We shall not share this information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

The clauses of this policy are valuable for all kinds of information gathered from Download Route users. Additional clauses, if any, will be added if necessary for special services that we may offer in the future. This privacy policy informs you about the type of personal data that we may collect from you, the way we can use it, the way we understand to protect it, who has access to it and how the possible mistakes can be corrected. 

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
There is information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by DownloadRoute.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by DownloadRoute.com for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DownloadRoute.com Web site.

DownloadRoute.com keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within DownloadRoute.com, in order to determine what DownloadRoute.com services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DownloadRoute.com to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. DownloadRoute.com uses web log analysis software on its server and keep the reports for internal use; DownloadRoute.com does not use these reports to identify individual users except in cases of deliberate mis-use of our systems.

DownloadRoute.com does not disclose email addresses; they are kept confidential, and greetings can only be sent via a web form which includes extensive protections against automated submission. We never sell e-mail addresses to third parties (for instance, to bulk e-mail advertisers). 

DownloadRoute.com does not sell nor make available to the public postal mail addresses, phone numbers, or other information gathered during business transactions or software submissions with our customers, software authors. DownloadRoute.com Web sites will disclose any personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DownloadRoute.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DownloadRoute.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DownloadRoute.com, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The DownloadRoute.com Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DownloadRoute.com pages, or register with any DownloadRoute.com services, a cookie helps supershareware.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DownloadRoute.com services or Web sites you visit.

**Ad Servers Privacy**  
We have contracted with Google AdSense to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Google AdSense may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. 

**Security of your Personal Information**  
DownloadRoute.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. DownloadRoute.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**External Links**  
DownloadRoute.com provides external links to other websites, mainly software developers websites . DownloadRoute.com is not responsible and cannot control the content and security of other sites you visit once you leave DownloadRoute.com website. Software programs made available at DownloadRoute.com website are hosted from servers all over the world. DownloadRoute.com does not host any software in its server. DownloadRoute.com makes no representations as to the content of externally hosted software files or that the files and programs are accurate, complete, virus-free or do not infringe the rights of any third party. When downloading, each user is responsible to virus check any program from the DownloadRoute.com site before installation. DownloadRoute.com is not responsible for any loss or damage resulting from users downloading or use of any such programs or files.

**Contact Information**  
DownloadRoute.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DownloadRoute.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us, We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

This Privacy Policy has been updated today, 24th of March, 2009.
